add0n.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy :: add0n.com

**1\. Information Collection and Use**

add0n.com will not collect any personally identifiable information about You - such as your name, address, telephone number or e-mail address - unless You provide it to add0n.com voluntarily and approve its use.

If You do not want Your personally identifiable information collected, please do not submit it to add0n.com. When You do provide add0n.com with personally identifiable information, it may use that information to better understand Your needs and how it can improve its products and services. add0n.com may also use that information to contact You, for example, to answer a question or respond to a comment You have submitted. add0n.com reserves the right to display any questions or comments You submit, without reference to your identity, together with any responses add0n.com provides, on its frequently asked questions page found at http://add0n.com/faq.html. In the case of requests for new pages, add0n.com will use Your information to assess Your request, to verify Your identity and the identity of Your other project contributors, and for any other reasonable purposes in connection with Your request. However, it will not provide Your information to third parties without your consent, except as required by law as explained in the "Information Sharing" section below.

In some cases, add0n.com may collect information that is not personally identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet browser or computer operating system You use, the date and time You visited the Site, the pages You accessed, and the name of the web site from which You linked to the Site. add0n.com uses this information to analyze trends and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

**2\. Information Collection and Use**

The Site hosts opt-in mailing lists and newsgroups for discussion about hosted projects and for general issues related to Browser application and extension development. Opt-in mailing lists may be found on the main site at http://add0n.com/mailing-lists.html and on the individual project pages. These mailing lists are bonded, which means they do not provide Your email address to third parties. If You have signed up for an opt-in mailing list and You later wish to opt-out, You may do this by following the instructions on the "mailing list" links on the relevant pages.

When you sign up on a mailing list on the Site, you may be sent newsletters and other announcements of interest to add0n.com, depending on which mailing list you opt-in to. For a description of the non-project specific mailing lists available, please go to http://add0n.com/mailing-lists.html.

You may have the opportunity to send an email to another user or mailing list, in which case Your valid email address and real name will be included in such messages. In order to prevent abuse, You may not opt-out of such a display, but may choose to refrain from transmitting the email message.

When participating in newsgroups or chat rooms, Your personal information may be publicly available through Your profile display, in which case You have the option to opt-out of publicly displaying Your real identity. Where site profiles allow users to display optional information publicly, such entry and display is at Your discretion and may be changed at any time by You.

The Site is an open source site and the data and information hosted on the Site is publically accessible by design. Anonymous messages (or posts that have been edited to be made anonymous) are against the spirit of open source. When You offer content for other add0n.com users to read, attaching Your name to it gives other add0n.com users the ability to reply to You privately about it, in case they feel that a public reply would be inappropriate. If You want to avoid spam, use mail filters, or refrain from posting on the Site. add0n.com will not be responsible for any unsolicited email that You receive as a result of You posting Your email address on the newsgroups, chat rooms, or mailing lists.

This privacy policy does not protect any information that You transmit to newsgroups, chat rooms, mailing lists or other users.

**3\. Cookies**

add0n.com may use "cookies" - very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites - on the Site. This information will be in the form of a cookie or similar file and will help add0n.com enhances its web experience by saving time on the Site. This can also make your next visit easier and the site more useful to you. In general cookies play an important role. Without them, using the web would be a much more frustrating experience. With most Internet browsers, you can easily erase cookies from Your computer's hard drive, block all cookies or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However these may stop our website from functioning properly. Please refer to Your browser instructions or "help" screen to learn more about these functions. add0n.com may use cookies for the following reasons: 

  * add0n.com allows you to share pages with some social networks such as Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Google Plus, Pinterest and Stumbleupon. Each of these networks has their own cookie policy. Please visit each social media website to see their cookie policies before sharing any content.
  * We also use Google Forms, Google Analytics and Google AdSense‎ in add0n.com. Google uses certain cookies in order to better operate on third-party websites. Please refer to [How Google uses cookies](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/), [How Google uses data when you use our partners' sites or apps](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/partners/), [How Google uses cookies in advertising](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/ads/) and [Google Analytics Cookie Usage on Websites](https://developers.google.com/analytics/devguides/collection/analyticsjs/cookie-usage). 
  * add0n.com uses PayPal module in order to place PayPal donation button on its pages. PayPal website and its modules may use certain cookies in order to operate. Please read about PayPal policies about cookies [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full#How_We_Use_Cookies_and_Similar_Technologies).
  * add0n.com uses Amazon.com services such as cloud front (CDN). Amazon has certain cookie policies regarding its services. To read more about Amazon's cookie policy please visit [Amazon.com Privacy Notice](http://www.amazon.com/gp/help/customer/display.html?nodeId=468496).
  * We also use several other public CDN servers to host certain modules in add0n.com. Each of these services may use certain cookies for different purposes. Please visit following pages to read more about each service's cookie policy: [MaxCDN's cookie policy](https://www.maxcdn.com/legal/), and [CloudFlare's cookie policy](https://www.cloudflare.com/security-policy).

**4\. Information Sharing**

Although add0n.com makes every effort to preserve user privacy, it may need to disclose information when required by law wherein it has a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on the Site.

**5\. Certain Third Party Transactions**

add0n.com may disclose personal information to third parties it engages to provide services that involve data processing on its behalf. Also, if some or all of the assets of add0n.com are sold to a third party, such third party will be entitled to use the personal information disclosed by You, but only in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

**5\. Security**

The Site has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under add0n.com's control. However, it is not possible to guarantee the security or integrity of information You disclose Online since a sufficiently powerful attack from an unauthorized third party could compromise your data.

**5\. Links to None-add0n.com Sites**

The Site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that add0n.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. add0n.com encourages You to be aware when You leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by the Site.

**6\. How to Contact add0n.com**

If You have any questions or suggestions regarding add0n.com's privacy policy, or if You have submitted personally identifiable information through the Site and would like access to such information or to have that information corrected, please [email us](mailto:support@add0n.com).
